export const lvl2 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What music festival takes place in Brisbane every year?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Big Day Out',
      'B) Brisbane Festival',
      'C) Woodford Folk Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What is the largest theatre in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Queensland Performing Arts Centre',
      'B) Sydney Opera House',
      'C) Melbourne Theatre Company',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Queensland Performing Arts Centre',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What art form is most popular in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Mixed media', 'B) Street art', 'C) Painting'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Street art',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What cultural center in Brisbane is dedicated to Australian art?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Queensland Art Gallery',
      'B) National Gallery of Australia',
      'C) Art Gallery of New South Wales',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Queensland Art Gallery',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What is the largest annual performing arts festival in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Comedy Festival',
      'B) Brisbane International Film Festival',
      'C) Brisbane Food and Wine Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane International Film Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `Which famous artist was born in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Edvard Munch', 'B) Jackson Pollock', 'C) Jeffrey Winter'],
    correctAnswer: 'C) Jeffrey Winter',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What musical style is associated with Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Hip-hop', 'B) Rock', 'C) Pop'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Rock',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What cultural event takes place in Brisbane in December?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Queensland Day',
      'B) Christmas in the City',
      'C) Australia Day',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Christmas in the City',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `Which famous architect designed the Queensland Art Gallery?`,
    answers: ['A) John Loughton', 'B) Ken Yeap', 'C) Richard Neidhamm'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Ken Yeap',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What establishment in Brisbane is famous for its street art?`,
    answers: ['A) Fortitude Valley', 'B) West End', 'C) South Bank'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) West End',
  },
];
